Zingo, spin around.
Do you want something good
Here you go.
He is quite disobedient.
This is Roboth Duke Duke ... which Alma has tested in collaboration with Silverlit.
If you saw "What's in the box" a few weeks ago you know we tested Robo Kombat, which became Harry's favorite.
Should we turn him off, right?
- Yes, we turn him off.
So, turned off.
Fy.
Here it says "Duke", but Alma has named him Zingo.
One records different ... what is it called
It is called...
When dressing, what is it called call?
No.
"Commands" is called in English.
Yes, "Commands".
Then the dog should do as you please, and it works pretty well.
Yes, but I'd rather have a real dog.
Yes of course.
It brings us into today's question, we will start this vlog with a day of the day.
Elina Larsson wonders: "Do you want some pets".
A robot dog.
From one animal to the other now we are going to the stable.
Should it be fun, right?
Yes
Alma has attended riding school during the fall.
Many of you have asked to see a vlog when we ride.
We asked Alma's riding school and they did not want us to film.
So we went out with a search on our Instagram.
Worst best thing.
- Yes indeed.
A girl named Emelie heard from us, so now we are on our way to her stable, Hästravaganza.
Yay
And ... Harry will try to ride for the first time
For the first time Yeah, Yeah, Yeah, Yeah, Yeah!
Merry Christmas (Merry Christmas)
Hello
Dad.
- Hi, Harry.
Welcome to Hästravaganza.
- Thanks!
We have the horses ready for you, we'll pick them up
What a luxury, Alma you do not need to sm in and scratch hoofs.
In here we have stuff to borrow.
- Oh, what a lot.
Then we will see what we can find.
- Different vests, here.
Yes exactly.
Here we have the most common.
Oh...
Oh, how hard it was.
Ouch.
Fully equipped.
Is this here we should?
- Yes.
Here we have Erik.
He will have today, he is a Norwegian fjord horse, an older gentleman.
Hello Hello.
- Hello Hello.
He didn't wave back.
Waving you have to wave back.
Here we have Dorina.
Hi, Dorina.
They are a little bigger than you are used to, Alma.
- Yes exactly.
Dorina is a Schwarzwald horse.
Are you nervous?
- No, I'm afraid.
Scared, scared!
She is very brilliant, she loves people.
And food.
Are you going to kiss her?
- No!
Should I kiss her?
- Yes.
No thanks, preferably not.
But I can pat her a little.
How's it going?
- Good.
Oh there is the track.
In with the foot here.
Nice.
Nice, Alma.
You must not roll down now.
Are you ready
Brave
Brave, brave, brave, brave, brave ...
Are you going to come to this pallet, or are you good there?
- I'm good here.
Okay, then we come to that pallet.
Oh ... This is going to be a little difficult to get up.
Stop the foot in this, left foot.
- The second foot.
So, and then over with the leg.
Dad Axel went off to have dinner with his dad and sisters, and we went home.
What do you think of the day?
- It's been fun.
It was fun to ride on another stable and on other horses, I have to say that.
Very, very fun.
I draw a dog.
It is obedient and it is called sweetie.
Are you hungry?
- Yes.
We will make our own pizza.
- Yay, yay, yay!
Harry, come and make pizza with us.
- No I'm busy.
You.
- Yes.
You are never so busy that you can't eat.
- But can I play a little while?
Alma, is it your towel that is here?
- Oh sorry.
I happened to forget it.
I showered after the stable.
Harry is starting to make his pizza, and I'm his assistant.
I need cheese.
- But Harry, you have to take tomato sauce first.
Yes exactly.
I had that on my last.
Thanks.
Sprinkle with it.
So there.
What was it like to ride?
- Fun.
It was the most fun to trot.
Then just ...
And then we ran faster ...
I ran like this.